♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
——·乜可里译制·——
我都干了些什么? 天啊 我干了些什么
What have I done? Oh, God, what have I done...
没事的 Jake
It's all right, Jake.
我们会陪你度过难关的
We'll get through this as a family.
对啊 别担心了 爸爸
Yeah, don't worry, Daddy.
无论发生什么事 你还有我们啊
We're here for you no matter what.
我快要错过"将到美景"了
I'm going to miss Upcoming Attractions!
发生什么事了?
What's wrong?
你爸在生意上遇到些小挫折 亲爱的
Your father had a little business setback, dear.
他失去了一个客户
He lost a client.
他说"我有个很棒的主意"
"I got a great idea," he said
"一个价值百万美元的主意"
"A million dollar idea," he said.
他说"给宠物抽的雪茄 你怎么看?"
"Cigars for pets. What do you think?" he said.
他说"我希望你可以老实回答"
"I want you to be honest," he said.
我特么地居然信他说实话了
What the hell made me believe him?
Jake 每个人都有说错话的时候
Jake, everyone slips up now and then.
他因为说实话把你解雇了?
He fired you for being honest?
这是一个圈套
It was entrapment!
就是说我和Qunin再也不用去那运动鞋血汗工厂咯?
So it's off to the sneaker sweatshop for me and Quinn?
你们两个别胡扯了
Don't be ridiculous, you two.
Daria 你知道我已经有很多事够忙的了
Daria, you know I've got more work than I can handle,
你会再忙起来的 Jacky
and you'll get busy again, Jakey.
只要再耐心等待一下
Just be patient.
那等的同时我要做什么呢?
But what'll I do in the meantime?
你不是总说你想要做烹饪嘛?
You always said you want to work on your cooking.
如果你想找点事让自己忙起来的话
If you're looking for some way to occupy yourself,
那里还有很多需要做的家务活
there are plenty of chores that need doing around here.
怎么了? 是你先说起的
What? You get to say it.
很好
Good.
Brittany 你挤颜料了吗?
Brittany, did you spill your paint?
没有?
Um, no?
请问现在方便吗 Defoe老师?
Is this a good time, Ms. Defoe?
方便 进来吧
Yes, come on in.
同学们 Li校长和O'Neill先生有些激动人心的事要告诉我们
Class, Ms. Li and Mr. O'Neill have some intriguing news.
我们朗岱尔高中参加了一个州际范围内的艺术比赛
Lawndale High is participating in a state-wide student art contest.
所以我们选择在美术课上来宣布这个消息
That's why we chosen art class is the place to announce it.
这个比赛的主题是"千禧年初期的学生生活"
The theme of the contest is "Student Life at the Dawn of the Millennium."
就是在这个日新月异的年代 高中学生的生活是怎样的
What's it like to be a high school student in today's fast-changing world.
当然 是否参加完全出于自愿 但说实话
Entry is strictly voluntary, of course, although frankly,
我认为你们都不应该放弃这个难得的机会
I don't see how any of you could think of passing up the chance
为自己和朗岱尔高中"到来"荣誉
to bring honor unto yourself and Lawndale High.
到来?
"Unto"?
系好我鞋带
Buckle my shoe.
出自小说名《One, two, buckle my shoe.》
Defoe老师将从每个班里挑选出参赛作品
Ms. Defoe will choose the entries from each art class,
而我则是我们学校这次比赛的协调员
and I'm contest coordinator for the school.
祝你们好运 孩子们
Good luck, kids!
同学们 我劝你们还是好好把握这次机会
Students, I urge you to take this opportunity.
好奇心 探索精神 表达方式
Curiosity... inquiry... expression...
这些都是教育过程中的主要模块
these are the building blocks of education.
校长?
Ma'am?
没有提问环节 祝你们好运
No questions! Good luck, all!
我想告诉她我有个很好的做海报的主意
I wanted to tell her I've got a great idea for a poster!
我也是
Me, too.
我的主意是关于拉拉队的
Mine's going to be about cheerleading.
不 那我要做什么?
Oh, no! Now what'll I do?
来橄榄球队担任四分卫怎么样 宝贝?
How about something on quarterbacks, babe?
Jane 你可以留下来几分钟吗?
Jane, can you stay a minute?
Jane 我很想知道所有的学生对这个比赛有什么看法
Jane, I'm eager to see what all the students come up with for this contest.
是所有那些选择参加的学生吧
All the students who choose to participate.
但我实在等不及想要看到你参加
But I really can't wait to see your entry.
但是 你知道 我不认为艺术家们之间要互相竞赛
Well, you know, I really don't think artists should compete with each other.
我只相信社区创造力
See, I believe in a community of creativity.
你是一个杰出的艺术家和一个原创型思考者
You're such an accomplished artist, and such an original thinker.
如果说这个学校谁能捕捉到当今学生的生活状况
If there's anyone in this school who can capture student life today,
那个人就是你
it's you.
我只是想说 祝你好运
I just want to say, good luck.
谢谢
Thanks.
她干嘛要表现那么亲和?
Why did she have to be so nice?
弄得我必须要想出些关于学生生活的愚蠢海报
Now I have to come up with some stupid poster about student life.
该从哪开始呢?
Where to start?
有那么多令我们憎恨的地方
There's so much to hate about it.
话说 没有人说一定要传达正面信息
You know, nobody said the message had to be positive.
我要做一些真正能够反映学生生活的海报
I'm going to do something that really represents student life.
对
Yes.
告诉人们高中生活是有多操蛋
And tell the truth about how much it can suck
对
Yes.
驱散掉那些故事书里所幻想的"年轻真好"的屁话
To blow away the story-book fantasy about how great it is to be young.
没错
Yes.
你要帮我一把
And you're going to help.
不要
No.
你一定要帮我一把
You gotta help me.
你是我认识最消极的人
You're the most negative person I know.
多谢夸奖
Thanks.
别这样嘛
Come on!
难得有机会能告诉全世界
Now's your chance to tell the world
你真心认为朗岱尔高中生活何等鸟样
what you really think of life at Lawndale High.
告诉世界 我 Daria Morgendorffer 有话要说
Tell the world that I, Daria Morgendorffer, have something I want to say.
没错
Yes!
不要
No.
来嘛 帮我一把
Come on!
好吧
All right.
我会做出我的个人陈述 并坚定不移地支持它
I'll make my personal statement, and I'll stand behind it.
我知道你会的
I knew you would.
但只在完全匿名的情况下
But only on condition of strict anonymity.
你才是真正的圣女贞德啊 你知道吗
You're a real Joan of Arc, you know that?
贞德被英国宗教法庭判为异教徒 绑在火柱上烧死
是吧 而且我觉得我离火柱不远了
Yeah, and I think I just ordered a stake.
你看取名"美国未来的接班人"怎么样?
How about we call it, "America's Future Leaders,"
我们要做的就是把Kevin和Brittany的照片放大
and we just enlarge a picture of Kevin and Brittany?
少来 那也太令人沮丧了吧
Come on, that's too depressing.
你觉得我们叫它
How about we call it,
"美丽只存在于肌肤深处" 然后我们贴上学生真正的皮肤?
"Beauty is only Skin Deep," and we attach the skin of an actual student?
这个我喜欢
Oh, I like that.
我在想能否劝Quinn把她的皮捐出来?
I wonder if we can talk Quinn into donating hers?
我开始在想这应该会需要很多的披萨
I'm starting to think this is going to require more pizza.
我开始同意你的看法了
I'm starting to agree with you.
我们说到哪了?
Where were we?
我们说到挂一卷捕蝇纸 然后称它为
We were talking about hanging a roll of fly paper and calling it,
"拥有吸引力的重要性"
"It's Important to Be Attractive."
那上面挂苍蝇还是不挂?
Oh, yeah. With or without flies?
他们有在披萨配料中多加了一夸脱油脂吗?
Did they add another quart of grease to the pizza recipe?
要再来一块吗?
One more slice?
不要了 我真觉得我快要吐了
No, I already feel like I might throw up.
见到那么多人参加这次比赛 我真的感到很高兴
Well, it's very gratifying to see so much participation in the contest.
Charles 你海报的名字叫什么?
Charles, what's the name of your poster?
我叫它"开起 Chucky 开起"
I call it, "Ride, Chucky, Ride."
它到底反映了现代学生生活的哪部分呢?
And what exactly does it say about student life at the century's edge?
这反映更多的是个人的目标陈述
It's more of a personal mission statement.
他是指不可能实现的目标
Mission impossible, he means.
给我们讲讲你的海报 Brittany
Tell us about your poster, Brittany.
我把它称做"拒绝饮酒与吸毒"
I call it, "Don't Drink or Take Drugs."
所反映的信息是 拒绝饮酒和吸毒
And the message is, don't drink or take drugs!
但我们怎么看得出它的意思呢?
But how do we get that message?
我看到的只有酒精和毒品
All I see is the alcohol and the drugs,
并没有什么否认标志说明它们的危险性啊
with no negative imagery to symbolize their dangers.
有了
There!
Brittany 这... 我们还是下课后再讨论吧
Well, Brittany, that's... um... let's talk after class.
Jane 你们打算怎么做?
And Jane, what did you decide?
她真漂亮
Oh, she's beautiful!
"她知道自己完爆别人了 没人敢比她更瘦
"She knows she's a winner, she couldn't be thinner,
于是她进了洗手间把吃的晚饭都吐了出来?"
now she goes in the bathroom and vomits up dinner?"
Jane 我觉得这并不好笑
Oh, Jane, I don't think that's funny.
你不觉得吗?
Um, you don't?
你认为拿有饮食失调的人来作乐很搞笑吗?
Do you think it's funny to make fun of someone with an eating disorder?
不 但是...
No! But...
这本来就不是拿来作乐的
It's not meant to be funny.
呃 那么
Well, then,
那你是要表达对一些形象比较不佳的人的偏见
do you think it's your place to pass judgement on someone with a low self-image
仅仅因为你自己没有这些问题吗?
just because you don't have that problem yourself?
但那根本不是我要说的啊
But that's not what I'm saying at all.
那你要说的是什么?
Then what are you saying?
我说的是人们不应该... 呃...
I'm saying that people shouldn't... uh...
她说的是现今太注重外貌是很危险的
She's saying that all the emphasis on appearance today can be dangerous.
这个女孩很漂亮
The girl is very pretty,
你的第一反应是"多快乐的青年啊"
and your first reaction is, "Oh, what a happy teenager!"
但也许并不是你看到的那样
But maybe that's not the whole story.
也许她们的美丽是要付出很高代价的
Maybe that prettiness comes at a price.
Jane 这就是你想说的吗?
Oh, is that what you're saying, Jane?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
那你一定要以这种毫无吸引力的图解语言表达出来嘛
And you felt you had to say it in such graphic, unappealing language.
是有意选择这样的语言表达的
The choice of words was deliberate,
为的是用这样的美丽形象吸引人
to contrast with the beauty of the image
然后给观者一种震撼 让他们警觉
and shock the viewer into paying attention.
你知道吗 Jane
You know what, Jane?
这真的是一件艺术品
This really is a work of art,
而它也以一种很原始的方式做出了声明
and it really does make a statement, in an original way.
希望你能带我和你们一起参加这个州际比赛
I'd like you to let me enter it in the state-wide competition.
听起来不错
Sounds okay.
那你的搭档有什么看法?
And how does it sound to your collaborator?
下次我会给你一个提前准备好的声明
Next time, I give you a prepared statement.
Daria Jane 这张海报真漂亮
Daria, Jane. This poster is beautiful
真是一幅杰作啊
Truly accomplished.
这是你们的荣誉 也是朗岱尔高中的荣誉
A real credit to yourselves and to Lawndale High.
还有那几句诗... 非常的抽象有趣
And the poem... a very interesting perspective.
除了...
Except...
除了什么?
Yes?
其中有一句
There's this one line.
嗯?
Yes?
我在想你们能否考虑
I'm just wondering if you would consider
把"晚饭都吐出来"那部分改改
changing the part about vomiting up dinner.
那有点恶心
It's kind of yucky.
它会表现出一种不雅的学生形象
It presents a distasteful picture to the student body.
你知道我们并不希望人们那样做
You know we wouldn't want people doing that.
有道理
That's the point.
那我们的意见一致咯
So we're all on the same page!
这个女孩太过于追求美丽
The girl is so obsessed with being beautiful
导致她在某一方面变得很极端
that it turns her into something really ugly.
这就是海报要表达的意思
That's the message of the poster.
花了我好一段时间构思呢
So it takes me a while.
但她看起来既美丽又快乐啊
But she looks so pretty and happy.
何不把主题表现得积极乐观呢?
Why not make the theme positive?
去掉"把吃的晚饭都吐了出来"
Instead of "she vomits up dinner,"
换成"她几乎没有动过晚餐"
how about "she barely touches dinner?"
你是说保持美丽太累了 以至于她根本没力气去吃东西了?
You mean, being that gorgeous is so tiring that she's too exhausted to eat?
就是这个意思
Exactly!
看吧 就算美丽的人也有烦恼
See, even beautiful people have problems.
所以 就围绕这个主题 孩子们
So, hang in there, kids!
你完全没了解我所表达的意思 对吧
Boy, you really don't get it at all, do you?
听着 我压根儿就不想写这些愚蠢的诗
Look, I didn't even want to write this stupid poem.
我才不在乎人们怎么对他们自己呢
I don't care about what other people do to themselves.
但是如果你改了那句
But if you change that line,
这首诗就变成传达另外一种虚伪的信息了
the poem becomes just another phony dishonest message.
它传达的和原来所传达的一样
It'll applaud the same thing it criticized before.
你难道没看出来吗?
Don't you see that?
Morgendorffer小姐
Ms. Morgendorffer,
年轻人看起来太骄傲不太好吧?
is it so wrong for young people to take pride in the way they look?
对这张海报 你想怎样就怎样吧
Do whatever you want to the poster.
不要写我的名字就好
Just take my name off it.
还有我的
And mine.
别急 小姐们 你们好像有点太激动了
Now, now, ladies. Emotions are running high.
我们花一天时间好好想想 你们看怎样?
Let's all take 24 hours to think about it, hmmm?
好吧
Fine.
你们自己做决定吧
It's your decision to make!
打电话给她们父母
Call their parents.
Jane Lane Amanda Lane女士
Jane Lane. Mrs. Amanda Lane.
你好吗 Lane女士
"Hello, Mrs. Lane!"
没人接 那就打给Helen Morgendorffer
Okay. Helen Morgendorffer.
你好 Morgendorffer女士
"Hello, Mrs. Morgendorffer!"
我三点钟完全没有事要做
I've got absolutely no paperwork for my three o'clock,
这个早上我都没有动力工作了
I can't find the brief I was supposed to get this morning,
还有我记录里的电邮地址还是错的
and my stationary still has the wrong e-mail address!
为毛这里没有一件事是顺心的?
Why the hell can't anything ever go right around here?
Helen? 是你女儿的老师
Helen? It's your daughter's teacher.
告诉他们我会让Quinn在星期一把作业交上去
Tell them I'll make sure Quinn turns in the assignment by Monday.
顺便问问作业是什么 好吗?
Oh, and try to find out what the assignment is, ok?
或者你可以开始记录下来
and maybe you could get started making a few notes on it.
是你另一个女儿 应该
It's your other daughter, I think.
Daria? 那好吧 告诉他们我会说说她的态度的
Daria? Well, then, tell them I'll talk to her about her attitude,
顺便问问她侮辱了谁 又说了什么
and try to find out who she insulted and what she said.
他说她有个很好的机会
He says that she has a rare opportunity
不想看到您女儿白白浪费掉
that he'd hate to see her squander...
电话给我 你好 我是Helen Morgendorffer
Oh, just give it to me. Helen Morgendorffer.
你好 Morgenfoffer女士 Morgendorffer
Hello, Mrs. Morgenfoffer... uh, Morgendorffer.
我是朗岱尔高中的Timothy O'Neill
This is Timothy O'Neill at Lawndale High.
我是您女儿Daria的英语老师
I'm your daughter Daria's English teacher.
你好 请问是关于...
Yes, is this about her essay
她《废除死刑而采取酷刑》的论文吗?
banning capital punishment and bringing back torture instead?
很明显她只是在开笑话
Because that was obviously a joke.
不 Morgendorffer女士 是关于她帮忙创作的一幅海报
No, Mrs. Morgendorffer, it's about a poster she helped create.
我们正在举行一个...
See, we're having a contest
关于千禧年初期的学生生活...
concerning student life at the dawn of the millennium...
请你能说快一点吗?
Could you possibly speed this up a little?
我快错过两个电话会议了
I'm late for two conference calls.
她给一幅很好的图片写了一段不太好的诗歌
Um, she wrote a very unpleasant poem to go with a very nice picture
希望您能跟她谈谈 也许能让她考虑重新写一段
and I was hoping you would talk to her about maybe reconsidering and rewriting it.
好的 我很乐意
Fine, I'll be happy to.
如果这件事还需要进一步讨论 请你致电给我丈夫吧
If this requires further discussion, please feel free to call my husband.
Jake Morgendorffer
Jake Morgendorffer.
你好 Morgendorffer先生
"Hello, Mr. Morgendorffer."
喂 我是Jake Morgendorffer Jake Morgendorffer在这里
Hello Jake Morgendorffer, Jake Morgendorffer here,
能为您做点什么? 有人在吗?
what can I do for you, anybody there?
你好?
Hello?
您已接通"咨询Jake Morgendorffer"的办公室
You've reached the office of Jake Morgendorffer Consulting.
你需要咨询人士帮助
You need to be consulted
谁还要一勺香蒜酱?
More penne a la pesto, anyone?
好吧
All right.
你的朋友Jane叫你帮她一起制作海报
You friend Jane asked you to help her make a poster.
如果发现是哪个虐待狂今天打电话给我...
If I ever find out who the sadist was who called today...
你想出了关于一个饮食失调的漂亮女生的主意
You came up with the idea of a pretty girl with an eating disorder.
是滴
Yep.
Daria 那真是太... 你了
Daria, that is so... you.
这是种赞美还是侮辱?
Is that a compliment or an insult?
话说 如果把这个冻在冰箱里
You know, if you refrigerate this stuff,
香蒜酱会变得有点发臭
the pesto kinda gets a little funky.
会氧化或发生别的化学变化
It oxidizes or something.
最好是当天做了当天吃
It's best eaten the day it's made.
谁还想再要一些?
Now, who would like some more?
Jake 你能把那该死通心粉放下吗
Jake, would you put down the damn macaroni
问下你女儿为什么她一定总是要那么愤世嫉俗
and ask your daughter why she has to be so cynical all the time!
这不是通心粉 Helen
It's not macaroni, Helen!
她本来应该做一幅有关学生生活的海报
She's supposed to be making a poster about student life,
但是她想的却是她能想出的最负面的信息
and she comes up with the most negative message she could think of.
这不叫负面
It's not negative.
这是正面 反映了学生不想被人单凭外表而断定他们
It's supportive of students who don't want to be judged by their looks.
算了吧 Daria 那样的人根本不存在
Oh, come on Daria. People like that don't exist.
Jake 问问她为什么就不能偶尔积极乐观一点
Jake, ask her why she can't be upbeat once in a while.
你看 Helen
You see, Helen,
如果这是通心粉和芝士 那将会多糟糕啊
if this was supposed to be macaroni and cheese, it would be very bad.
但这是香蒜酱
But it's penne a la pesto,
如果以香蒜酱的标准去评判 这一盆可是极好的
and judged by the standards of penne a la pesto, it's very good.
Jake 你到底在说什么? 你有认真听吗?
Jake, what the hell are you talking about? Are you listening?
当然有
Of course, sure.
我的意思是
What I mean is,
如果这是一幅提高学生生活的宣传海报 那真是太糟糕了
if this poster is supposed to be propaganda promoting student life, it's very bad.
但如果它作为一种表达Daria对学生生活的个人观点的艺术
But if it's supposed to be art expressing Daria's personal vision of student life,
那很棒 你觉得呢?
it's very good. See?
谢了 老爸
Thanks, Dad!
在氧化了
It's oxidizing.
就这样 啪
So then, splat!
倒在了我爸头上 晚饭结束了
Dinner ends up on top of my dad's head.
太棒了
Wow, excellent.
你的年少轻狂正在将你的家庭撕裂
Your youthful integrity is tearing your family apart.
并不全是
Well, not exactly.
我妈回来跟我叨念了什么经前不快症状 跟我道歉了
My mother came back and mumbled something about PMS and apologized,
但至少我们今晚不用吃剩下的通心粉了
but at least we don't have to eat leftover macaroni tonight.
我们还在坚持退出那个海报比赛 对吧?
We're still resigning from the poster contest, right?
Daira?
Daria?
我告诉他们我至少会听O'Neill先生的意见
I told them I'd at least listen to Mr. O'Neill's point of view,
但我并没有做出任何承诺
but I didn't make any promises.
我是说 除了那个之外
I mean, other than that one.
你们看 我并没想要改变你们对这幅海报原本的意图
So you see, girls, I don't want to change the intent of your poster.
只是想让它更积极和谐一点
I just want to make it more palatable.
就像他们说的 一勺糖能帮助你把苦药吃下去
You know what they say, a spoonful of sugar helps the medicine go down.
如果你有糖尿病那就不管用了
Not if you're diabetic.
打断下 O'Neill先生
Excuse me, Mr. O'Neill?
怎么了?
Uh, yes?
我想要用我的新海报参加比赛
I want to enter my new poster in the contest.
这张真是不错
Oh, that's really nice.
表达出多积极的信息啊 是团结主题吗?
What an affirmative message. Togetherness?
表达的信息是 "不要加入帮派"
Um, the message is, "don't join a gang."
这也是标题
That's also the title.
Brittany 我看到了帮派
Um, Brittany, I see the gang,
但貌似没看到有什么东西表明了"不要"
but I don't see anything representing "don't."
是嘛
Oh, yeah.
我唇膏哪去了?
Where's my lipstick?
也是好作品变成牛逼作品的利器
And that's how good art becomes great art.
不管怎样 我有个主意
Anyway, I have an idea.
不如你们让我来写这段话如何?
How about you let me work on the poem a bit?
也许我能想出一些比较没那么伤人...
Maybe I can come up with something that's less abrasive,
而且符合你们意思的句子
that gets your point across.
如果我们不喜欢你想的怎么办?
And if we don't like what you do?
那就不用管它了 就让它按照你们原来设想的那样做
Then we'll forget about it and leave the poster the way you made it.
你们怎样都不吃亏 好不好?
You can't lose. What do you say?
迪士尼影史上获奥斯卡成就最高的作品
好吧 但要是再引用《欢乐满人间》就不跟你玩了
Okay, but quote Mary Poppins again and the deal's off.
Lane小姐 Morgendorffer小姐
Ms. Lane and Ms. Morgendorffer,
相信你们一定会对O'Neill先生即将展示给你们看的感到满意
I believe you're going to be pleased with what Mr. O'Neill has to show you.
Daria Jane 我真觉得我做到了
Daria, Jane, I really think I've done it!
我把那个较粗糙的部分变得更柔和
I've captured the essence of your message
抓住了你们要表达的意思的实质
while softening the rough edges.
你砂洗过它?
You stone-washed it?
"她知道自己完爆别人了 没人敢比她更瘦"
"She knows she's a winner, she couldn't be thinner,
因为她对于早中晚三餐所吃的东西都很谨慎
cause she's careful what she eats for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
合理膳食万岁"
Good nutrition rules."
你在开玩笑吗?
Is this a joke?
合理膳食习惯可不是笑话 Daria
Smart eating habits are no joke, Daria.
这跟我们的海报有毛关系?
What does this have to do with out poster?
把要传达的消极信息变成了积极信息
It turns a negative message into a positive one.
她不漂亮是因为她经常不吃东西
She's not pretty because she starves herself into it,
她很漂亮是因为她爱护她自己
she's pretty because she takes care of herself.
这比原来的表达更有力 因为非常的积极乐观
It's even more powerful than before, because it's upbeat!
我懂了 她再也不会吐了
I see. She's not going to throw up anymore.
但我可能会
But I might.
别那样做
Don't do that.
那很负面消极
It's downbeat.
你们这些年轻人应该感谢O'Neill先生
You young women should be thanking Mr. O'Neill
辛苦把你们想表达的信息有所保留
for his hard work preserving your message.
他没有保留它 他是歪曲了它
He didn't preserve it. He perverted it.
他把所有实质和影响 变成了没有意义的废话
He removed all the substance and impact and turned it into meaningless drivel.
我们只想要回我们原来的作品
So we'd like our poster back now, please.
什么意思?
Meaning what?
意思是 根据我们的协议 我们要退出这个比赛
Meaning we're withdrawing it from the contest, according to our agreement.
对不起小姐们 我可没有做出任何协议
Excuse me, girls, I didn't make any agreement.
O'Neill先生做了
Mr. O'Neill did.
O'Neill先生没资格跟你们做出这样的协议
Mr. O'Neill is in no position to offer such a deal.
这个海报会在明晚的学校董事会会议中展出
The poster will be displayed during the school board meeting tomorrow night
然后将会拿去参加比赛
then it will be entered into the contest,
最终给你们和我们带来荣...
and it will bring honor and acclaim to you two and to our...
但Li校长 我确实保证...
But Ms. Li, I did promise...
我没保证
I didn't.
她可以那样做吗?
Can she do that?
不能 这都是太多的香蒜味通心粉带来的噩梦
No, this is all a horrible dream brought on by too much penne a la pesto.
我们不要寻求帮助或什么吗?
Don't we have a recourse or anything?
能和O'Neill先生谈谈吗?
Can we talk to Mr. O'Neill?
我们可以说服他
We could appeal to him,
或许他会用他的压倒性人格压倒Li校长
and he might turn the full force of his overwhelming personality on Ms. Li,
然后 她会把他吃掉
and then she'd eat him.
那找你父母怎么样?
Well, how about your mother?
找你父母怎样?
How about yours?
我妈现在有点忙
My mother's a little preoccupied right now.
她在追踪干燥室里不明热气变化的来源
She's tracking down the source of a disturbing heat variation in her kiln.
但你妈妈可是个律师
But your mother is a lawyer.
一个认为我去参加这个海报比赛...
A lawyer who thinks it's a really good idea
是一个很好主意的律师
for me to get involved in the poster contest.
制度太让人失望了
The system failed us.
去他的制度
The system sucks.
我们必须从制度外出发
We're going to have to go outside the system.
你的意思不是...
You don't mean...
就是那个意思
Yes.
这事找我 你们算是找对人了
You did the right thing coming to me.
抱歉把你吵醒了
Sorry we woke you up.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
这也是迟早发生的事
It was bound to happen sooner or later.
好吧 计划是这样的
All right, here's the plan.
我会坐在这里随时准备加大马力踩油门
I'll sit right here with my foot on the accelerator, ready to burn rubber.
Trent 把车熄火放到那边
Trent, pull over here and make sure you turn off the car
小心你睡着了 好吗?
in case you fall asleep, okay?
B计划 酷
Alternate plan. Cool.
海报大赛参赛作品
警报解除了吗?
All clear?
准备解除
Just about.
等等
Wait.
你们两个在这儿干嘛?
What are you guys doing here?
观察
Observing.
清白的
Innocently.
真不敢相信Li校长对你们海报所做的事
I can't believe what Ms. Li did to your poster.
等等... 你们两个想要干什么?
Wait a minute... what are you guys planning?
走开 Landon
Get lost, Landon.
为你自身考虑
For your own good.
你前程大好 妹子
You've got a bright future, kid.
你不想在这儿跟着一些将要变坏的东西一起变坏吧
You don't want to be here when what's going to go down goes down.
我们行动吧
Let's do it.
怎么回事?!
What?!
不
Oh, no!
你们真以为你们可以逃脱掉责任吗?
Did you really think you were going to get away with this?
现在说"可以"是很愚蠢的吧
Well, it would be stupid to say "yes" now.
我没开玩笑
This is no joke!
故意毁坏学校财产是会受到惩罚的犯罪
Vandalizing school property is a punishable offense,
我们要做的第一件事就是打电话给你们父母
and the first thing we're going to do is call your parents!
算了
Oh, bother!
在这周边 我应该拍谁的马屁
Whose butt do I have to kiss around here
才能在傍晚前拿到我的局间邮件?
to get my interoffice mail before nightfall?
Helen 是你女儿学校的校长打来的
Helen? It's your daughter's school. The principal.
校长?
The principal?
你好
Hello?
你好 Morgendorffer女士
Hello, Mrs. Morgendorffer.
我是Angela Li 朗岱尔高中的校长
This is Angela Li, principal of Lawndale High.
你好 Li校长 请问有什么能帮你?
Yes, Ms. Li. How may I help you?
Morgendorffer女士 恐怕我有一些坏消息要告诉你
Mrs. Morgendorffer, I'm afraid I have some rather bad news.
您的女儿Daria 她涉嫌故意毁坏学校财产
Your daughter, Daria, appears to have been involved in an act of vandalism.
什么?
What?!
Morgendorffer女士
Mrs. Morgendorffer,
您的女儿和Jane Lane一起
your daughter collaborated with Jane Lane
为一次艺术比赛创作了一幅海报
in the creation of a poster for our art contest.
是的 我知道
Yes, I'm aware of that.
我们发现海报的一部分很不合宜
We found part of the poster unacceptable,
所以在参赛前修改了一点
so it was altered prior to its entry.
很不幸的是 有人在海报展出的时候把它毁坏了
Unfortunately, someone defaced the poster while it was on display,
考虑到您女儿还有Lane小姐曾反对修改这幅海报
and since your daughter and Ms. Lane had objected to changing it,
我很确定他们就是损坏海报的人
I must assume that they were the vandals.
恐怕我要对他们采取严厉的措施
I'm afraid I'm going to have to take drastic action.
等等
Wait a moment.
你说她们曾经反对修改海报
You're saying the girls were against changing the poster,
但还是让它去参加比赛了?
but entered it into the contest anyway?
这是为她们着想
It was entered for them.
我记得这个比赛的参加是以自愿为原则的吧?
I was under the impression that participation in this contest was voluntary.
是自愿 但是您的女儿不自愿参加
It was, but your daughter refused to volunteer,
按她的情况 我就得强制她参加了
so in her case, I made it mandatory.
好吧 Li校长 让我这样跟你说吧
All right, Ms. Li, let me make sure I have this straight.
你把我女儿的海报拿走 修改了其中的意图
You took my daughter's poster from her, altered its content,
在她不愿意的情况下拿去展览
exhibited it against her will,
现在还要对她进行处分
and are now threatening discipline
因为你说她毁坏了她自己的财产
because you claim she defaced her own property,
就是你说的偷窃?
which you admit to stealing?
这根本不是我要说的
That's not what I said at all!
Li校长 请问你对"侵犯公民自由"这个短语熟悉吗?
Ms. Li, are you familiar with the phrase "violation of civil liberties"?
我...
I...
还有"吃官司"
And the phrase "big fat lawsuit"?
所以唯一能拯救我们作品的方法就是毁掉它
So, the only way for us to save our work was to destroy it.
这话真上口
Catchy phrase.
而且还不用受罚
And we got away with it.
你应该把这事写成一个小故事
You should turn this into a short story.
不失为一个好主意
That's not a bad idea.
我想我已经想好题目了
And I think I already have a title for it.
什么题目?
Yeah?
我打算叫它 "千禧年初期的学生生活"
I'm going to call it, "Student Life at the Dawn of the New Millennium."
赢了 艺术比赛我赢了
I won! I won the art contest!
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组